Do you know about Jun Seo and Eun Seo?
They love each other.
They are in love.
Jun Seo, you...
You...
Dad, no.
It's not his fault.
I'm the one who loves him.
He doesn't love me back.
What does this all mean?
Jun Seo.
Is it true?
Yes.
(Episode 9)
Why did you do that?
You should've told them it was not true.
Well?
I didn't want to lie.
Jun Seo.
Eun Seo.
We should leave.
Choi Eun Seo.
Eun Seo.
Thank you.
What do you mean they left?
I am not sure.
What do you mean?
Tae Seok, tell me. What did you mean?
Are you saying they ran away?
Eun Seo.
Give me the key. I'll drive.
They'll be back soon.
They probably have so much on their minds.
They ran away? That's nonsense.
So, don't worry, Tae Seok. All right?
Their parents were in shock.
They could've talked tomorrow
if they had had to.
Stop it.
Stop.
Stop talking, please.
Choi Eun Seo.
Eun Seo.
Do you regret it?
No, I don't.
Can I sleep?
Can I go to sleep?
Don't go anywhere, okay?
I think we'll get punished.
Don't worry.
I'll take whatever is coming to us.
I'll get punished for us both, Eun Seo.
What can I do?
What should I do?
He's not here.
Jun Seo is not here.
He is nowhere.
What can I do if they really ran away?
What should I do?
(Off)
Here we go.
- Enjoy.
- Thanks.
Eat up.
Right, is that so?
How is your mother?
She is well.
You have not changed at all.
Nonsense, I got really old.
By the way...
Who is he?
He is...
You are lucky I have a vacant room.
It is a humble room,
but I hope you don't mind.
I like it.
Thank you.
Thank you so much.
You're very welcome.
This is good.
But I think it feels empty somehow.
Why don't we go and buy things?
Sure.
What is that for? Is it for me?
I've never picked up men's clothes.
I have no idea. You choose.
No, you pick one for me.
You dress well.
I don't know what style you like.
I'll wear whatever you choose from now on.
So, pick one for me.
- This one.
- What?
Then, this is for you.
After you left for the U.S.,
my family came here
to run away from our debts.
Mom worked at the farm,
and I finished school
while helping with errands.
Did you?
I experienced my first love here.
What?
It caused much drama.
I cried and wrote letters all the time.
Who was he?
That's a secret.
I engraved names on a tree.
Did you?
So you did that, all right.
- Are you jealous?
- No.
Which tree would be a good pick?
Engrave my name... right away.
Jun Seo. When are we going back?
When will we?
It's my birthday in a few days.
Can we go back after my birthday?
Let me see. Today is...
Your birthday is the day after tomorrow.
We can't, can we?
Everyone is probably
waiting for us to come back.
Will they forgive us?
I don't care.
I don't care if they don't forgive us.
When I came here, I gave up on everything.
When I asked you to leave with me,
I gave up everything.
Jun Seo.
I left everything to be with you.
I won't think about anything else.
Do you get that?
There it is.
I found it.
My tree.
Eun Seo, come back.
I'm waiting for you.
Choi Eun Seo. Come back now.
Have you got a death wish?
I'll kill you for this.
Eun Seo.
Choi Eun Seo.
The mailbox is full.
You cannot leave a message.
Hello.
I have more to say.
I...
have more to say.
I love you, Eun Seo.
Hello.
What...
What are you talking about?
What do you mean Eun Seo ran away?
Why would she run away with her brother?
Why would she run away with Jun Seo?
I knew she would do something...
when he hit me, saying his Eun Seo
or whatever.
He's not even her brother,
and she is living with him.
All right.
I'll go. Stop giving me that look.
Director Han, I'll be waiting outside.
You two can talk.
What do you mean?
Is it true?
It can't be.
He's her brother. Her brother.
Are you sure you're not mistaken?
Is it real?
Is Eun Seo really...
Don't worry. I will take care of it.
Ms. Soon Im, please tell me.
Do you know anywhere she might be?
Eun Seo is with her brother...
With her brother?
It doesn't make sense at all.
What is wrong with her twisted fate?
It will be all right.
I will bring her back.
I will bring her back...
and get married to her.
Everything will be okay, Ms. Soon Im.
What do you mean by disciplinary action
against Choi Eun Seo?
She is on vacation.
How could she be on vacation...
when she eloped with a man at night?
Did you say she eloped?
Don't you know what elope means?
Running away!
A moonlight flit.
If you want to defend your subordinate,
you should know better about her.
We had better fire her.
I heard it is an affair.
Do you know anything about it?
An affair?
It doesn't make any sense.
She's such a decent girl.
He's a well-behaved man.
They might be desperate enough
to run away.
It seems that everyone is a mess
in their family now.
To their parents, they are real siblings.
But they're not related biologically.
They also have significant others
they promised to marry.
I know that.
But I also knew something else.
What did you know?
- That this could happen.
- That they would run away?
We seem to want it to happen.
I'm envious of them.
So am I.
Not everyone has that kind of love.
I found it.
My tree.
(Yoon Jun Seo, Yoon Eun Seo)
I experienced my first love here.
Who was he?
That's a secret.
I engraved names on a tree.
Jun Seo.
What are you doing?
Yes?
Isn't it pretty?
Is this for me?
No, it isn't.
You are mean.
About your first love...
Yes?
Never mind.
Since when did you like me?
It's an awkward question, isn't it?
I'm not sure.
What about you?
I'm not sure, either.
But what you said about
wanting to be a tree...
I kept that in my mind.
I think I'm very strong.
Think about it.
I said I wanted to be a tree.
If I were to take root in one place,
I would be heartbroken
if things were to go wrong.
I wouldn't be able to move...
or be moved.
If it hurts, are you going to move?
No.
I won't even if it hurts.
I'll always be by your side loving you.
Even if you won't look back at me,
I'll live my life looking at you.
I will.
I'll do that, too.
I'll always look at you.
Happy birthday.
Thanks.
Eun Seo.
Please marry me.
I was your first love, wasn't I?
Mom, let me do it.
Sit.
You should go to work after breakfast.
Honey, are you all right?
Can you sit up like this?
Have a seat.
Today is...
Eun Seo's birthday, honey.
What are you going to do?
Aren't you going to do anything?
You should report this to the police.
Exactly what can we report to them?
Then what?
Are we to do nothing, without a clue
as to where they are?
We'll wait.
Jun Seo will come back.
They used to be brother and sister.
I can't let this happen.
I can't talk about it to anyone.
I don't know about that.
I don't know.
Think about it.
It is a shame on our family.
A shame?
Whose fault do you think this is?
It's all because of you. It's your fault.
You decided to leave for the U.S.
leaving Eun Seo behind.
Honey.
It is Eun Seo's birthday.
It's also my birthday.
Sin Ae.
I knew this could happen
when Eun Seo showed up.
I knew it.
Sin Ae.
Eun Seo.
What are you doing alone?
He went out to buy something.
Did he?
Eun Seo.
You are getting married to him,
aren't you?
Yes.
Send my regards to your mom.
Tell her to keep in touch, okay?
Yes.
Okay.
Hello.
Eun Seo.
Mom, it's me.
I called to let you know I'm fine.
Eun Seo.
Eun Seo, don't hang up.
Don't hang up, Eun Seo.
Why are you doing this?
Why do you have to do this?
Where are you?
Do come back now! Do come back now!
I'm sorry.
But I'm happy.
I'm so happy.
I'm so happy here.
Did you say you're happy?
How could you say that?
Do you really think you're happy?
I heard he has a fiancée.
What about the man who likes you?
How can you be happy when you're breaking
your parents' hearts?
You'll get punished.
It'll all get back to you.
I'm sorry, Mom.
Don't worry about me. I'm doing well.
I am...
at the farm.
I called you to let you know
that I'm doing well.
Mom.
Are you at the farm?
How could you go there?
Do you really think you're happy?
How can you be happy
when you're breaking...
your parents' hearts?
You'll get punished.
It'll all get back to you.
Eun Seo.
What's wrong?
Stay still.
Sit.
- Are you all right?
- Yes.
Jun Seo, I'm fine.
Stay still. Lean your head back.
Are you all right?
Did it stop?
Yes, it stopped.
- Were you scared?
- Yes, I was.
I should be sick all the time, then.
What?
I would like you to rush toward me
with concern.
Isn't this a cake?
So you went out to buy this?
Yes.
Did something happen to you?
No.
I'm just happy.
I'm scared because I'm so happy.
I'm silly, right?
Yes, you are.
This is what you asked to be
delivered by today.
And what about
the dinner reservation for tonight?
Cancel it, please.
Yes, I will.
Hello.
Where is she?
I am sorry.
The wretch must be out of her mind.
That is the only reason she's doing this.
I want to go and drag her here right now.
But I haven't worked for a while,
so I don't have any money.
Also, I'm hungry...
Where is she?
I know I shouldn't do this.
I...
I wouldn't do this if I had a decent job.
Where is she?
Cheers.
Happy birthday.
Thanks.
Have some cake.
Let's eat.
Let's go back tomorrow.
Yes, let's go back.
Are you sad?
There's no need to be sad.
We go back tomorrow
and tell them we're getting married.
Then we can come back here
after getting married.
Don't you want to?
When we go back...
It'll be all right.
I'll take care of everything.
You don't need to do anything.
Don't listen to anyone,
and don't see anything.
You should see and listen to only me.
That is all you need to do.
Don't do that.
You don't need to do that.
Let's not do that, Jun Seo.
I have had enough now.
It's enough for me to be with you
right now.
Don't do that.
If you do that...
to my mom, your mom and dad,
and other people, it won't be proper.
We can't do that
just to make ourselves happy.
I have had enough,
so let's not do that, Jun Seo.
It's not enough for me.
It wouldn't be enough
even if I lived with you forever.
What can I do?
- It's getting colder.
- Yes.
Tae Seok.
Eun Seo and I...
are getting married.
Yoon Jun Seo.
Think about it again.
You and Eun Seo can't get married.
No.
Your parents and Yu Mi.
You can't leave them.
Even if you do it now,
you're not that kind of a person.
You're not capable of it.
Yoon Jun Seo.
How could you do that?
How could you do that to Yu Mi?
How could you do that to your parents?
How...
How could you do that to me?
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, Tae Seok.
But Eun Seo and I...
We'll get married.
Let's go back in the morning.
Take the front seat.
I said, take the front seat.
You don't get to sit together
in front of me.
I'll get it.
It is Yu Mi's mother.
- Mom, why are you doing this?
- Let me go.
Mom.
I have no words to say to you.
What is wrong with your family?
How could he run away with a girl
who is almost his sister?
Mom.
Don't say anything.
I am sorry.
I trusted Professor Yoon.
That is why I let Yu Mi date Jun Seo.
How could you do this to us?
You shouldn't have let them
get engaged, then.
They will be back.
I promise you they will be back.
Please wait for them.
And what if they are back?
Do you think we can leave this behind us?
We will break off their engagement.
Mom, what are you doing?
I can't live without Jun Seo. I can't.
Keep yourself together.
Mom, do you want to see me die?
How could you...
How could you do this?
We are sorry.
Eun Seo.
Jun Seo.
Jun Seo, you.
Yoon Jun Seo.
We are sorry.
We...
will get married.
Jun Seo.
Get out, Eun Seo.
Eun Seo.
Haven't you ever loved me,
not even for a little bit?
I'm sorry.
Don't forgive me.
Please don't forgive me.
I'm sorry.
There is nothing I can do but this, Yu Mi.
It's fine, Choi Eun Seo.
You can live the way you live.
I'll live the way I do.
What?
Is she still alive? Right?